A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Technology, 2000-2009 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Technology, 2000-2009 (bulk 2006-2009)
The Library of Virginia
44703
7.4 cu. ft. (17 boxes)
Virginia. Secretary of Technology.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 44703 transferred by Brian Chiglinsky, 1111 E. Broad St., Richmond, Va., 14 January 2010.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Secretary of Technology is responsible for the efficient and effective use of information technology to simplify government operations, advance technology applications to improve public services, and drive the innovation economy through the Commonwealth's leadership. The position oversees two agencies: the Virginia Information Technologies Agency and the Center for Innovative Technology. The Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA) is led by Virginia's Chief Information Officer and is responsible for all of the information technology needs of Virginia's Executive Branch agencies. The Chief Information Officer reported to and was appointed by the Information Technology Investment Board, until the board was reorganized in 2010. The Secretary of Technology served as an ex-officio member of the Information Technology Investment Board and as its vice-chair. The Center for Innovative Technology is tasked with creating, retaining and attracting technology-based jobs and businesses to Virginia.
Aneesh Chopra was nominated to be the fourth Virginia Secretary of Technology on 14 January 2006, taking over from Eugene Huang. Prior to his nomination, Chopra worked for the Advisory Board Company and served on the Virginia Board of Medical Assistance Services and the Southern Technology Council. Chopra served in this position until leaving to become the first Chief Technology Officer of the United States under President Barack Obama.
Leonard Pomata was nominated to be the fifth Virginia Secretary of Technology in June 2009 due to the vacancy created by the resignation of Aneesh Chopra. Pomata served in this position until the end of Tim Kaine's administration.
Scope and Content
This collection contains the records, 2000-2009 (bulk 2006-2009), of the Virginia Secretary of Technology. Includes correspondence and subject files, which contain information on the inward-facing aspects of the Office of the Secretary of Technology. There are also special projects and studies which relate to health care, higher education, access to broadband internet, intellectual property, and interoperability. Legislative files contain information relating to bills of interest to the Secretary of Technology. Finally, there is material from the meetings of the Information Technology Investment Board.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and subject files
Series II. Special projects and studies
Series III. Legislative files
Series IV. Information Technology Investment Board
Wherever possible, the original order of the files has been maintained.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and subject files, 2000-2009., 1.8 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
  Correspondence and subject files, 2000-2009, which contain information on the inward-facing aspects of the Office of the Secretary of Technology. Includes correspondence with other Executive Branch agencies, members of Congress, and the General Assembly. There are also constituent letters, typically sent to Governor Tim Kaine and then assigned to the Secretary of Technology. Finally, there is information related to the Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, the Virginia Center for Innovative Technology, and the Virginia Information Technologies Agency.
  Wherever possible, the original order of the files has been maintained.
  - Congressional and legislative correspondence, 2006-2009. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Southside Cabinet Day thank you letters, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letters sent to Ambassadors, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letters upon which the Secretary of Technology was copied, 2006-2008. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constituent letters, 2007-2008. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constituent letters, 2006-2007. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Constituent letters, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constituent letters, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Constituent letters, 2007-2009. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Council on Virginia's Future meeting, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Council on Virginia's Future meeting, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Small, Women, and Minority Owned Businesses, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget material, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Decision brief copies, 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2006-2009. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Governor's cabinet retreat, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management Participant Handbook, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cost savings, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Entrepreneurial development, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Technology Research Fund, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Technology Research Fund Distribution, 2003-2006. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Research and technology Advisory Commission, 2006-2007. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Emerging Technology Fund in Texas, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Grant Allocation Committee meeting, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission Research and Development Subcommittee, 2005-2007. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium on-site briefing book, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium on-site briefing book, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, 2008. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Center for Innovative Technology, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Center for Innovative Technology Board of Directors, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency Surveys, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 2008. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency memoranda of understanding, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Longwood University memorandum of understanding, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series II. Special projects and studies, 2002-2009., 2 cu. ft. (5 boxes)
  Special projects and studies, 2002-2009, of the Secretary of Technology. The special projects and studies include of reports, notes, correspondence, meeting agendas, and meeting minutes and are typically outward-facing. There are projects related to health care, higher education, access to broadband internet, intellectual property, and interoperability, among others.
  - Governor's Commission on Biotechnology, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Virginia Report, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - University-Based Partnerships in Economic Development, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Workforce Meetings of the States, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Governor's Business One Stop Decision Package, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Feasibility Study for Deploying Interoperability Channels Executive Summary, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Feasibility Study for Deploying Interoperability Channels Final Report, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Interoperability Baseline Assessment Report Executive Summary, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Interoperability Baseline Assessment Report Final Report, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Virginia University Research Parternship Organizational Meeting, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Council on Virginia's Future Meeting, 2008. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Bioscience Legislative Caucus, 2008. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Broadband Roundtable, 2008. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Draft Higher Education Agreements, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Public-Private Education and Infrastructure Act, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - VCU International Agenda, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Medicaid transfer grant, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Health information technology, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Teletrack, 2009. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Virginia broadband stimulus applications, 2009. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Aerospace Council, 2008-2009. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Applications for higher education restructuring, 2009. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cooperative contract reports, 2009. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Intellectual property and patent information from universities, 2006-2009. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Broadband access, 2007-2008. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Shore Broadband, 2006-2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Student Training and Refurbishment Program, 2008-2009. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Achieve Healthcare Information Systems, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Health information technology website, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Health Records Taskforce, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Health information technology meeting notes, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Health Information Technology Council, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Health Information Technology Council grants, round two, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - EMPI, undated. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Workforce training, undated. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Health Records Store Duffield, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Health Plan and Health System Summit on Administrative Data Exchange, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Health Information Technology Council: MedVirginia, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Health Information Exchanges, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Health information technology archive, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Solutions Group, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - North Highland Identity Management, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Solutions Group project review, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Louis Engagement, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Workforce training, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Security dashboard, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Governor's Health Information Technology Council, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Veterans services, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Health Information Technology Council, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Healthcare Foundation, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Health information technology, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Health information technology log, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Health Information Technology Council committee meeting, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Health Information Technology Council meeting, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Health Information Technology Council meetings, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Health Information Technology Council meeting, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Series III. Legislative files, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.8 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
  Legislative files, 2006-2009, of bills of interest to the Secretary of Technology. Each file may include a legislative action summary, in which the agency affected and the Secretary of Technology give their recommendations on whether to support or oppose a bill; a copy of the bill as introduced; correspondence and notes relating to the bill; fiscal impact statements from the Department of Planning and Budget; and, if the bill passed, an enrolled bill review, in which the agency affected and the Secretary of Technology give their recommendations as to whether the Governor should sign or veto the bill.
  - Secretary of Technology's Information Book, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Technology's Information Book, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - HB 400 (Wittman): Broadband, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - SB 433 (Davis): Electronic records, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - SB 292 (Cuccinelli): Sexually explicit email penalty, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - HB 1154 (Lingamfelter): Security breach notification, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - HJR 25 (Cosgrove), 2006. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - HB 1603 (Rapp): E-911, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - HB 1079 (Scott): Broadband, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - HB 329 (Purkey): Tech and biotech investment, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - HB 458 (Rust): Public Procurement Act, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - HB 134 (Cosgrove): Higher education intellectual property, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - HB 75 (Purkey): Venture capital, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - HB 1244 (Hugo): Tech Career Grant Program, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - SB 76 (Houck): Freedom of Information Act, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - HB 1508 (Plum): Database breach notification, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - SB 174 (Wampler): Public-Private Parternship Commission, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - SB 316 (Howell): Sex offender registry, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - SB 541 (Stosch): Public-Private Partnership Advisory Commission, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - SB 465 (Edwards): FOIA; electronic communications, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - HB 254 (Cosgrove): Computer trespass, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - HB 1239 and HB 1241: PPEA Bills, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - VITA Watch Bills, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - HB 1069 (Hall): Department of Minority Business Enterprise, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - HB 122 (Marshall): Minority business, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - HB 563 (Nixon): Court records, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - HB 1198 (Marshall): Voice over IP, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - SB 395 (Stolle): Wireless E-911 Services Board, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - SB 21 (Mims): Internet and the Code of Virginia, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - HB 68 (Callahan): Clerks' fees, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - HB 984 (Sherwood): Sex offender registry, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - SB 559 (Stolle): Sex offender registry, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - SB 433 (Devolites): Comp BD Payment Bill, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Technology Bills, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Other bills of interest, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - HB 1603 (Rapp): Multiline telephone systems; owner or operator thereof ability to identify location from 9-1-1 call, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - HB 1723 (Peace): Year 2000 references; eliminates references to problems arising therefrom, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - HB 1885 (Marshall): Voice-over-Internet protocol service; revises definition, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - HB 1917 (Ward): Public Procurement Act; require disclosure of location where services are to be performed, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - HB 1939 (Purkey): Technology, Nanotechnology and Biotechnology Investment Fund; created, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - HB 2030 (Cosgrove): Modeling and Simulation Advisory Council; created, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - HB 2137 (Cline): State agencies; procurement of services by certain, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - HB 2140 (Brink): Identity theft; notification of breach of information system, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - HB 2196 (Nixon): Chief Information Officer; powers and duties, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - HB 2198 (Nixon) Electronic medical records, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - HB 3114 (Cosgrove): Aerospace Advisory Council, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - HB 2275 (Purkey): Nanotechnology Authority Act of 2007; created, report, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - HB 2306 (Callahan): Higher educational institutions; operational authority for areas of information technology, etc., 2007. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - HB 2381 (May): Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act; wireless broadband services, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - HB 2870 (McEachin): Cellular telephones; encouraged to program with ICE numbers, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - HB 2946 (Plum): Electronics disposal and recycling; policies thereof are consistent with data, etc. policies, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - HB 2973 (Bell): Unsolicited bulk electronic messages; changes scope of State's spam law, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - HB 3148 (Bulova): Compromised Data Disclosure Act; created, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - HB 3171 (Landes): Economic Development Partnership Authority; General Assembly may appropriate grants thereto, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - SB 756 (Stosch): Public-Private Partnership Advisory Commission; created, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - SB 845 (Devolites-Davis): State agencies; Chief Information Officer to develop policies, etc. relating to security data, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - SB 861 (Reynolds): Public Procurement Act; required disclosure of location where services are performed under contract, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - SB 1004 (Devolites-Davis): Telework, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SB 1006 (Saslaw): Commonwealth Innovations Incentive Fund; created, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SB 1224 (Howell): Identity theft; notification of breach of information system, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - SB 1029 (O'Brien): Chief Information Officer; provide for security of state government electronic information, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SB 1342 (Houck): Higher educational institutions; operational authority therefor in areas of procurement, etc., 2007. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SB 1408 (Hanger): Competition Council; required to review procurement process, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2007 Session. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Annual Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Data breach bills, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - HB 1017 (Hugo): Telework Promotion and Broadband Assistance, Office of; established, report, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - HB 1018 (Hugo): Telecommuting; definition, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - HB 1019 (Hugo): Telecommuting; state agencies to keep savings, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - HB 1021 (Hugo): Telecommuting; establishes goal for state agencies, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - HB 1030 (Frederick): Telecommuting; state contractors to offer to employees, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - HB 1031 (Frederick): Income tax, corporate; telework expenses tax credit, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - HB 1329 (Peace): Communication towers, state-owned; wireless broadband service in unserved areas, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - HB 1563 (J. Scott): Telecommuting; Secretary of Technology report annually to General Assembly, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - SB 193 (Herring): Income tax, corporate; telework expenses tax credit, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - SB 206 (Stuart): Communication towers, state-owned; wireless broadband service in unserved areas, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - SB 132 (Houck): Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act; disclosure of personal information, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - HB 634 (May): Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act; disclosure of personal information, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - HB 955 (Nixon and Scott): Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002; definition of qualifying projects, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - HB 352 (Stosch): Motor carriers; liability insurance for buses with capacity of no more than 40 passengers, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - HB 578 (Cosgrove): Innovative Technology Authority; powers of board of directors, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - HB 234 (Cosgrove): Technology Research Fund; adds sensor sciences to eligible research programs, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - HB 595 (D. Marshall): State officials and employees; payment of state funds for certain communication devices prohibited., 2008. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - HB 90 (Nichols): Public Procurement Act; verification of legal presence of contractors for employment, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - HB 390 (Bulova): Compromised Data Notification Act; created, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - HB 416 (Marshall): Innovative Technology Authority and Center; repealed, adding certain Funds, report, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - HB 497 (Cosgrove): Center for Innovative Technology; duties, report, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - SB 585 (Cuccinelli): Planning and Budget, Director of Department; required to have searchable budget database website, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - HB 748 (Caputo): Innovative Technology Authority; board of directors, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - HB 909 (Purkey): Nanotechnology Authority Act of 2007; created, report, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - HB 1458 (Cosgrove): Freedom of Information Act; records and meetings of Innovative Technology Authority., 2008. (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - HB 1500 (Lewis): Aerospace bill, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - HB 910 (Purkey): Technology, Nanotechnology and Biotechnology Investment Fund; created, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - HB 1504 (Nixon and Byron): Compromised Data Notification Act; created, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - SB 426 (Barber): Public Procurement Act; verification of legal presence of contractors for employment, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - SB 319 (Wagner): Technology Research Fund; adds sensor sciences to eligible research programs, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SB 235 (Whipple): Innovative Technology Authority; powers of board of directors, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SB 236 (Whipple): Innovative Technology Authority; board of directors, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - SB 726 (Petersen): Freedom of Information Act; exempts from public disclosure certain proprietary records, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 2008 Session. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Annual Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - SB 1477 (Locke) Aerospace council, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SB 892 (McDougle): Information technology projects; Governor to include a biennial appropriation therefor, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SB 833 (Locke): Notaries public; electronic notarization to be developed by Secretary of Commonwealth, etc., 2009. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - SB 935 (Smith): VITA security, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - SB 1097 (Herring): Telework tax credit, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - SB 936 (Cuccinelli): VEAP budget database, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - SB 1173 (Watkins): Patent and copyright, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - HB 2499 (Alexander): Aerospace council, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - SB 1336 (Puckett): Broadband Advisory Council; established, report, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - SB 1164 (Watkins): E-911, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - SB 1153 (McDougle): PPEA, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - HB 2423 (May): BB Council, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - SB 1163 (Watkins): E-911, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - SB 1318 (Houck): Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act; extends implementation, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - SB 1244 (Stosch): Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002; qualifying project definition, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - SB 1456 (Petersen): Innovation and Entrepreneurship Investment Authority; created by merging, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - SB 1472 (Saslaw): Pre-paid wireless, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - SB 1472 (Saslaw): E-911, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - HB 1660 (J. Scott): Telework, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - HB 1845 (Lingamfelter): Security clause, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - HB 2022 (Rust): VITA bill, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - HB 2023 (Rust): VITA bill, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - HB 2044 (Nixon): Health IT bill, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - HB 2201 (Vanderhye): ITA-VRTAC Merger, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - HB 2285 (Cline): Budget database, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - HB 2415 (Bauchard): Technology Research Fund; robotics and unmanned vehicle systems, etc., to eligible research programs, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 32)